mockupworld.co 2019-04-01

# Privacy Policy | MockupWorld

_This Privacy Policy was last modified and published on May 22, 2018 and will take effect on May 25, 2018._

In order for Mockup World to operate the site needs to gather, process and store data. The following gives a simple overview of what happens to your personal information when you visit Mockup World. Personal information is any data with which you could be personally identified. Detailed information on the subject of data protection can be found in our privacy policy found below. Mockup World takes the protection of your personal data very seriously and treats it as confidential and in accordance with the statutory data protection regulations and this privacy policy. This privacy policy explains what information we collect and what we use it for. It also explains how and for what purpose this happens.

### General Questions

**Who is responsible for the data collection on this website?**

The data collected on this website are processed by the website operator. The operator’s contact details can be found in the website’s legal notice.

**How does Mockup World collect your data?**

Some data are collected when you directly provide it to Mockup World. This could, for example, be data you enter on a contact form. Other data are collected automatically by IT systems when you visit the website. These data are primarily technical data such as the browser and operating system you are using or when you accessed the page. These data are collected automatically as soon as you enter our website.

**What does Mockup World use your data for?**

Part of the data is collected to ensure the proper functioning of the website. Other data can be used to analyze how visitors use the site in order to optimize the content. Third-party advertisers might use the data to evaluate the results of running campaigns.

**Analytics and third-party tools**

When visiting our website, statistical analyses may be made of your surfing behavior. This happens primarily using cookies and analytics. The analysis of your surfing behavior is usually anonymous, i.e. Mockup World will not be able to identify you from this data. You can object to this analysis or prevent it by not using certain tools. This page will inform you below about how to exercise your options in this regard.

**What rights do you have regarding your data?**

You always have the right to request information about your stored data, its origin, its recipients, and the purpose of its collection at no charge. You also have the right to request that it be corrected, blocked, or deleted. You can contact Mockup World at any time using the address given in the legal notice if you have further questions about the issue of privacy and data protection. You may also, of course, file a complaint with the competent regulatory authorities.

### Cookies

To provide you with the best possible experience on our website, Mockup World may use cookies, as described here. By clicking accept, closing this banner, or continuing to browse our websites, you consent to the use of such cookies. Cookies consist of portions of code installed in the browser that assist the Owner in providing the Service according to the purposes described. Mockup World uses Cookies to carry out activities that are strictly necessary for the operation of this website, for example in relation to the distribution of traffic.

Some of the services listed below collect statistics in an anonymized and aggregated form and may not require the consent of the User or may be managed directly by the Owner – depending on how they are described – without the help of third parties. If any third party operated services are listed among the tools below, these may be used to track Users’ browsing habits – in addition to the information specified herein and without the Owner’s knowledge. Please refer to the privacy policy of the listed services for detailed information. Where the installation of Cookies is based on consent, such consent can be freely withdrawn at any time following the instructions provided on this page.

### Google Analytics

Traffic analysis helps Mockup World to identify popular parts of the site, such as mockups genres or other services and shows ways in which way to grow. That is why the site uses Google Analytics, a web analysis service of Google Inc, (1600 Amphitheatre Parkway Mountain View, CA 94043, USA; “Google”). The use includes the “Universal Analytics” operating mode. This facilitates the assignment of data, sessions, and interactions across several devices to a pseudonymous user ID and thus the analysis of a user’s activities across devices. 

Google Analytics uses cookies, which are text files placed on your computer, to allow the website operator to analyze how users use the site. The information generated by the cookie about your use of this website is usually transferred to a Google server in the USA and stored there. IP anonymization is activated on this website, that means Google will reduce your IP address within Member States of the European Union or in other states party to the Agreement on the European Economic Area beforehand. Only in exceptional cases will the full IP address be transmitted to a Google server in the USA and shortened there. The IP address transmitted by your browser in the context of Google Analytics is not merged with other Google data. On behalf of the operator of this website, Google will use this information to evaluate your use of the website, to compile reports on website activity and to provide the website operator with other services related to website and Internet use. The legitimate interest in data processing also lies in these purposes. The legal basis for the use of Google Analytics is § 15 para. 3 TMG and Art. 6 para. 1 lit. f GDPR. The data sent by us and linked to cookies, user-identifiers (e.g. User-IDs) or advertising-identifiers are automatically deleted after 14 months. Data whose retention period has been reached is automatically deleted once a month. For more information on terms of use and data protection, please visit <https://www.google.com/analytics/terms/gb.html> or <https://policies.google.com/?hl=en>.

You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser, however, please note that if you do this you may not be able to use the full functionality of this website. You can also prevent Google from collecting the data generated by the cookie and relating to your use of the website (including your IP address) and from processing this data by Google by downloading and installing the [Browser Add-on](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en). Opt-out cookies prevent the future collection of your data when you visit this website. To prevent Universal Analytics from collecting data across several devices, you must opt-out on all systems used. If you click here, the opt-out cookie will be set:  

Disable Google Analytics

A written and signed Data Processing Agreement with Google does exist.

### Newsletter – Mailerlite

Mockup World offers a free weekly newsletter that offers news about the latest additions to the catalog, exclusive free mockups, and updates on current freebies that you can find on the web. In order to sign up, you will have to share your first name and your email address. Mockup World only use this data to send the requested information and does not pass it on to third parties.

The newsletter subscription is managed by the European mail service provider [MailerLite](https://www.mailerlite.com/). In order to sign up, you will only be asked to leave your email address, that will be sent to Mailerlite where it will be stored in accordance with European and German data privacy laws. Mailerlite undertakes all pertinent precautions in order to preserve the security of the data and, in particular, to protect them against any accidental or unlawful destruction, accidental loss, corruption, unauthorized circulation or access, as well as against any other form of unlawful processing or disclosure to unauthorized persons. Mailerlite’s data storage center has information storage security certificate (ISO 27001) as well as a certificate of IT service management (ISO 20000). After your registration, you will receive a mail for your explicit subscription confirmation (double opt-in). Mailerlite does also offer analytics functions that show which and how many emails have been sent and opened, if mailings have bounced or which mails caused users to unsubscribe. The analytics are group-related and are not used for individual tracking. 

You may unsubscribe from this newsletter at any time by sending a mail to [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) or by clicking the “unsubscribe” link you’ll find in every mail. After unsubscribing your data will get deleted.

A written and signed Data Processing Agreement with Mailerlite does exist.

### Contact Forms

You can reach Mockup World in several ways, one of which is the contact form. In order to start a communication, you will need to share your first name and your email address using the contact form (encrypted page). Sending your message will create an email. Your personal information and the message do not get stored on website servers. In order to avoid spam each form uses the spam protection tool Google reCAPTCHA, a service provided by Google Inc. The use of reCAPTCHA is subject to the Google [privacy policy](https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=policies) and terms of use. Please note that data transmitted via the internet (e.g. via email communication) may be subject to security breaches. Complete protection of your data from third-party access is not possible.

### Advertising

This type of service allows user data to be utilized for advertising communication purposes displayed in the form of banners and other advertisements on this website, possibly based on user interests. This does not mean that all Personal Data are used for this purpose. Information and conditions of use are shown below. Some of the services listed below may use Cookies to identify Users or they may use the behavioral retargeting technique, i.e. displaying ads tailored to the user’s interests and behavior, including those detected outside this website. For more information, please check the privacy policies of the relevant services. In addition to any opt-out offered by any of the services below, the user may opt out of a third-party service’s use of cookies by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative opt-out page.  
http://optout.networkadvertising.org/

**BuySellAds (BuySellAds.com Inc.)** BuySellAds is an advertising service provided by BuySellAds.com Inc.  
Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data ([Privacy Policy](https://buysellads.com/about/privacy))  
Place of processing: United States 

**Freestar (Freestar Inc.)** Freestar is an advertising service provided by Freestar.  
Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data ([Privacy Policy](https://freestar.io/data-policy/))  
Place of processing: United States 

**Google AdSense (Google Inc.)** Google AdSense is an advertising service provided by Google Inc. This service uses the “Doubleclick” Cookie, which tracks use of this website and User behavior concerning ads, products and services offered. Users may decide to disable all the Doubleclick Cookies by clicking on [this link](https://wwwgoogle.com/settings/ads/onweb/optout).  
Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data ([Privacy Policy](https://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/))  
Place of processing: United States  
Privacy Shield participant.

### Commercial affiliation

This type of service allows this website like Mockup World to display advertisements for third-party products or services. Ads can be displayed either as advertising links or as banners using various kinds of graphics or links. Clicks on the link, icon or banner posted on the website are tracked by the third-party services listed below, and are shared with this website. For details of which data are collected, please refer to the privacy policy of each service: DealJumbo ([link](https://dealjumbo.com/)), DesignBundles ([link](https://designbundles.net/)), FontBundles ([link](https://fontbundles.net/)), CreativeMarket ([link](https://creativemarket.com/)), Envato ([link](https://envato.com/)), MightyDeals ([link](https://www.mightydeals.com/)), DesignCuts ([link](https://www.designcuts.com/)) 

### Social Media

**Facebook plugins (Like & Share buttons)**  
Our website includes plugins for the social network Facebook, Facebook Inc., 1 Hacker Way, Menlo Park, California 94025, USA. The Facebook plugins can be recognized by the Facebook logo or the Like button on our site. For an overview of Facebook plugins, visit [this page](https://developers.facebook.com/docs/plugins/). When you visit our site, a direct connection between your browser and the Facebook server is established via the plugin. This enables Facebook to receive information that you have visited our site from your IP address. If you click on the Facebook “Like button” while you are logged into your Facebook account, you can link the content of our site to your Facebook profile. This allows Facebook to associate visits to our site with your user account. Please note that, as the operator of this site, we have no knowledge of the content of the data transmitted to Facebook or of how Facebook uses these data. For more information, please see Facebook’s [privacy policy](https://de-de.facebook.com/policy.php). If you do not want Facebook to associate your visit to our site with your Facebook account, please log out of your Facebook account.

**Twitter plugin**  
Functions of the Twitter service have been integrated into our website and app. These features are offered by Twitter Inc., 1355 Market Street, Suite 900, San Francisco, CA 94103, USA. When you use Twitter and the “Retweet” function, the websites you visit are connected to your Twitter account and made known to other users. In doing so, data will also be transferred to Twitter. We would like to point out that, as the provider of these pages, Mockup World has no knowledge of the content of the data transmitted or how it will be used by Twitter. For more information on Twitter’s [privacy policy](https://twitter.com/privacy). Your privacy preferences with Twitter can be modified in your [account settings](https://twitter.com/account/settings).

### External content

Mockup World allows you to view content hosted on external platforms directly from the pages of this website and interact with them. This type of service might still collect web traffic data for the pages where the service is installed, even when users do not use it. 

**Google Fonts (Google Inc.)** Google Fonts is a typeface visualization service provided by Google Inc. that allows this website to incorporate content of this kind on its pages.  
Personal Data collected: Usage Data and various types of Data as specified in the [privacy policy](https://policies.google.com/privacy) of the service.  
Place of processing: United States  
Privacy Shield participant

**YouTube video widget (Google Inc.)** YouTube is a video content visualization service provided by Google Inc. that allows this website to incorporate content of this kind on its pages.  
Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data  
Place of processing: United States ([Privacy Policy](https://policies.google.com/privacy)).

### SSL encryption

Mockup World uses SSL or TLS encryption for security reasons and for the protection of the transmission of confidential content, such as the inquiries you send to Mockup World as the site operator. You can recognize an encrypted connection in your browser’s address line when it changes from “http://” to “https://” and the lock icon is displayed in your browser’s address bar. If SSL or TLS encryption is activated, the data you transfer to the site cannot be read by third parties.

### Hosting

In order to operate the site and avoid misuse of the service the log file of the ISO 27001-certified server stores the IP address, the browser visitors use, the time and date of the visits, and the system that visitors use. Teh hoster Hetzner only stores pseudonymized IP addresses of visitors to the website. At the web server level, this happens by default by storing an IP address 123.123.123.XXX in the log file instead of the visitor’s actual IP address, for example, 123.123.123.123. The “XXX” is a random value between 1 and 254, so it is no longer possible to establish the true identity of the visitor.

### Cloudflare

This type of service allows this website to distribute their content using servers located across different countries and to optimize their performance. Which Personal Data are processed depends on the characteristics and the way these services are implemented. Their function is to filter communications between this website and the User’s browser. Considering the widespread distribution of this system, it is difficult to determine the locations to which the contents that may contain Personal Information User are transferred. CloudFlare (Cloudflare) CloudFlare is a traffic optimization and distribution service provided by CloudFlare Inc. The way CloudFlare is integrated means that it filters all the traffic through this website, i.e., communication between this website and the User’s browser, while also allowing analytical data from this website to be collected.  
Personal Data collected: Cookies and various types of Data as specified in the [privacy policy](https://www.cloudflare.com/security-policy/) of the service.  
Place of processing: United States 

A written and signed Data Processing Agreement with Cloudflare does exist.

### The rights of Users

Users may exercise certain rights regarding their data processed by Mockup World. In particular, users have the right to do the following:

  * Withdraw their consent at any time. Users have the right to withdraw consent where they have previously given their consent to the processing of their Personal Data.
  * Object to processing of their Data. Users have the right to object to the processing of their Data if the processing is carried out on a legal basis other than consent. Further details are provided in the dedicated section above.
  * Access their Data. Users have the right to learn if Data is being processed by the Owner, obtain disclosure regarding certain aspects of the processing and obtain a copy of the Data undergoing processing.
  * Verify and seek rectification. Users have the right to verify the accuracy of their Data and ask for it to be updated or corrected.
  * Restrict the processing of their Data. Users have the right, under certain circumstances, to restrict the processing of their Data. In this case, the Owner will not process their Data for any purpose other than storing it.
  * Have their Personal Data deleted or otherwise removed. Users have the right, under certain circumstances, to obtain the erasure of their Data from the Owner.
  * Receive their Data and have it transferred to another controller. Users have the right to receive their Data in a structured, commonly used and machine readable format and, if technically feasible, to have it transmitted to another controller without any hindrance. This provision is applicable provided that the Data is processed by automated means and that the processing is based on the User’s consent, on a contract which the User is part of or on pre-contractual obligations thereof.
  * Lodge a complaint. Users have the right to bring a claim before their competent data protection authority.

Where Personal Data is processed for a public interest, in the exercise of an official authority vested in the Owner or for the purposes of the legitimate interests pursued by the Owner, Users may object to such processing by providing a ground related to their particular situation to justify the objection. Users must know that, however, should their Personal Data be processed for direct marketing purposes, they can object to that processing at any time without providing any justification. To learn, whether the Owner is processing Personal Data for direct marketing purposes, Users may refer to the relevant sections of this document.

Any requests to exercise User rights can be directed to the Owner through the contact details provided in this document. These requests can be exercised free of charge and will be addressed by the Owner as early as possible and always within one month.

### Changes to this privacy policy

The Owner reserves the right to make changes to this privacy policy at any time by giving notice to its Users on this page and possibly within this Website and/or – as far as technically and legally feasible – sending a notice to Users via any contact information available to the Owner. It is strongly recommended to check this page often, referring to the date of the last modification listed at the bottom. 

Should the changes affect processing activities performed on the basis of the User’s consent, the Owner shall collect new consent from the User, where required.

Date: 22.05.2018
